Jamie Leviner

Software Engineer Born 1980 in Florence, SC



About me

For the past 5 years, I have worked as a full stack software engineer with a concentration on front-end architecture, frameworks, and tooling. I am strongly interested in becoming part of a development culture that improves and enables its people, and I am looking forward to facing some new challenges.

Skills



Contact



✓ levinerjamie@gmail.com

(843) 229-1193

§ jamieleviner.com

jamieleviner

Experience

Software Engineer

ACS Technologies
July 2017 - present
Programming and watching cute cat videos.

Software Engineer-Associate

ACS Technologies July 2016 - July 2017 Fulfillment of extremely important tasks.

Software Development Apprentice

ACS Technologies August 2015 - July 2016 Making coffee and baking cookies.

Intern

ACS Technologies May 2015 - August 2016

Education

B.S. in Computer Science, Minor in Applied Mathematics

January 2011 - December 2014

Francis Marion University, Florence, SC 29501

<>> Projects

best-resume-ever

jamieleviner.com

Jekyll

Build fast A and easy multiple beautiful resumes and create your best jekyll theme Jalpc. CV ever! Made with Vue and LESS.

My personal website. Created using the jekyll theme Jalpc.